<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Offutt Air Show</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_basic">BasicActivity</string>
    <string name="Contact_Activity_Label">Contact</string>
    <string name="Social_Media_Activity_Label">Social Media</string>
    <string name="Attractions_Activity_Label">Attractions</string>
    <string name="Main_Default_Marquee">Offutt Air Show 2016. July 30-31. More info at <a href="www.google.com">OffuttAirShow.com</a>. No Coolers, Backpacks, or Pets.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_performers">PerformersActivity</string>
    <string name="Performers_Activity_Label">Performers</string>
    <string name="FAQ_Activity_Label">FAQ</string>
    <string name="Bike_Park_Activity_Label"><![CDATA[Bike & Park]]></string>
    <string name="Kid_Zone_Activity_Label">Kid\'s Zone</string>
    <string name="Sponsors_Activity_Label">Sponsors</string>
    <string name="Directions_Activity_Label">Directions</string>
    <string name="About_Offutt_Activity_Label">About Offutt</string>
    <string name="SM_facebook_link">http://www.facebook.com</string>
    <string name="SM_flickr_link">http://www.flickr.com</string>
    <string name="SM_pinterest_link">http://www.pinterest.com</string>
    <string name="SM_whatsapp_link">http://www.whatsapp.com</string>
    <string name="SM_twitter_link">https://www.twitter.com</string>
    <string name="Map_Activity_Label">Map</string>
    <string name="Schedule_Activity_Label">Schedule</string>

    <string-array name="performers">
        <item>USAF Thunderbirds|On May 25, 1953, the Air Force\’s official air demonstration team, designated the 3600th Air Demonstration Unit, was activated at Luke Air Force Base, Ariz. The unit adopted the name “Thunderbirds,” influenced in part by the strong Native American culture and folklore from the southwestern United States where Luke Air Force Base is located. The Thunderbirds program objectives are to support Air Force recruiting and retention programs, reinforce public confidence and professional competence of the Air Force, strengthen moral and esprit de corps among Air Force members, support Air Force community relations and people-to-people programs, and represent the US and its armed forces to foreign nations.|http://www.afthunderbirds.com/site/</item>
        <item>VFA-122 Super Hornet DEMO|The Tactical Demonstration, or "Tac Demo" team flies the single-seat F/A-18E and two-seat F/A-18F as close to the "edge of the envelope" as safety and prudence allow.  The routine highlights the Rhino\'s maneuverability and slow-speed handling characteristics and has been very well received around the country. |http://www.vfa122.navy.mil/demo.html</item>
        <item>Lima Lima Flight Team|The Lima Lima Flight Team started with one flying club. The Mentor Flyers, Inc. was organized as a non-profit corporation in 1975. It was chartered as a 15-member flying club, based at Naper Aero Club field, Outside of Naperville, Illinois. The Lima Lima Flight Team demonstration is flown with six airplanes, It includes several formation configurations, from the six ship wedge and double arrowhead, to the basic finger four and diamond formations. The team has developed a series of formation aerobatics maneuvers which demonstrate the full range of the T-34 performance envelope. Lima Lima has performed in airshows from coast to coast and border to border, thrilling more than 100 million spectators with the beauty and grace of their precision performances.|https://limalima.com/</item>
        <item>Kent Pietsch Airshows|Kent Pietsch fell in love with flying when he was four years-old. Five decades later, his passion has not waned. While most aerobatic performers have one basic program, Kent executes three storied acts that leave spectators mesmerized. These include a dead-stick (turning the engine off) routine from 6,000 feet and a rooftop landing on a moving RV! However, Kent is best known for a comedy act that features a detached aileron (wing flap) and a mesmerizing wingtip-scraping pass down the runway that you must see to believe. When Kent is at the controls of his plane, it is impossible not to watch him perform|http://www.kentpietschairshows.com/pietsch/Welcome.html</item>
        <item>P-51 Gunfighter|Gunfighter is one of the world\’s most famous P-51s, having appeared on the airshow circuit and providing rides for over 35 years. The aircraft is a P-51 "D" model, serial number 44-73264. Today, only about 150 airworthy examples of Mustangs exist world-wide in museums, flying or under restoration.|http://www.p51gunfighter.com/</item>
        <item>SNJ-6 "Texan"|Pilot: Hailing from Overland Park, KS, RADIAL RUMBLE pilot Jeff Shetterly is a third generation aviator who grew up in Indianapolis, IN and works in the medical device industry. Jeff graduated from the United States Military Academy at West Point with a degree in Human Factors Engineering and served in the United States Army on M1A1 Abrams tanks. He was stationed in Germany and deployed several times to the Balkans, leaving military service in 2001.\n\nAircraft: SNJ-6 "Texan"\nLenth: 29 ft\nWingspan: 42 ft\nWing Area: 253.7 ft2\nHeight: 11 ft 8 in\nEmpty Weight: 4,158 lb\nTop speed: 208 mph at 5,000 ft|http://www.radialrumble.com/</item>
        <item>Rifle Airshows|Pilot: Joe "Rifle" Shetterly is an active member of the USAF where he flies the venerable A-10 Thunderbold II (Warthog).  "Rifle" is an active instructor pilot who has logged more than 5000 hours in 133 different make/models of aircraft.\nAircraft: RV-8 is a highly polished member of the most prolific family of homebuilt aircraft ever made.  N76540 is a beautifully built example with a unique history.  The N-number tells the story of the builder (Eugene Gaddis) who served as a fighter pilot in the United States Air Force.  The N-number stands for the jets that Gene flew during his time as a military aviator: 7 is for A-7, 6 – F106, 5 – F5, 4 – F104, and 0 represents the F-100 and the A-10.|http://rifleairshows.com/</item>
        <item>G &amp; M Airshows|One of the most common questions asked is what does G&amp;M stand for?  The answer is Greg and Micki Shetterly!  Greg and Micki both have extensive backgrounds in aviation.  Greg built and flies the One Design, while Micki flies the Citabria around to shows allowing them to offer media and VIP rides.  Micki also announces for Greg while he flies the show.  After the show both of them will walk the flight line and visit with guests and help inspire the next generation of aviation enthusiasts.|http://g-and-mairshows.com/</item>
        <item>MIG-17 Randy Ball|Randy W. Ball / MiG Pilot, is North America\’s Premier Jet Demonstration Pilot. Randy has performed well over 1,000 performances to date! No other North American Jet Demo pilot even comes close to that number of performances. In fact, Randy is the only Jet Demo pilot (military or civilian) to be granted both a day and night unlimited aerobatic rating in jet fighters by the FAA.|http://www.fighterjets.com/</item>
        <item>TORA 101-Zero|TORA 101 is a Japanese A6M Zero replica originally used in the movie Tora! Tora! Tora! TORA 101 is realistic looking, has an authentic sounding engine with three-bladed propeller, LOUD wing mounted propane machine guns, and a smoke system.|http://www.tora101.com/torahome.htm</item>
        <item>Scott Francis Airshows|Scott Francis received his private license in high school and logged 2600 hours in more than 40 types of aircraft. He began flying aerobatics competitions in 2003, achieving the top level of "unlimted". Scott has been perfoming in air shows since 2006 and is currently flying the ultra-high performance MXS aircraft.|http://www.scottfrancisairshows.com/</item>
        <item>Dave Buchanan Airshows|Dan was a New York &amp; Connecticut home builder and flat-track motorcycle racer; then moved to Lake Tahoe, CA where he enjoyed the thrill of flying off mountain tops. He received his Private Pilot License in 1981 and completed his first air show in 1989. Dan is also a licensed pyrotechnician and a Commercial Glider pilot. Dan\'s unpowered hang glider (used in daytime act) is designed by NorthWing in Wenatchee, WA (NorthWing.com). His hang gliders are registered with the FAA as experimental aircraft (N numbers).|http://www.danbuchananairshows.com/</item>
        <item>SOCOM Para-Commandos|The Para-Commandos perform precision freefall parachute demonstrations across the United States, informing the public about the Special Operations Command, it\'s mission, and the great work being performed by the Special Operations Command\'s Soldiers, Sailors, Marines and Airmen deployed to over 100 countries around the world. The team normally jumps from an altitude of 12,500 feet above the ground, freefalling approximately 2 miles and reaching speeds in excess of 120 miles per hour wearing smoke canisters on their feet to make them visible to the public below. |http://www.socom.mil/Pages/CommandParachuteTeam.aspx</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="statics">
        <item>B-25 Mitchell Bomber|Named for famed airpower pioneer Brigadier General William “Billy” Mitchell, it was a twin-tail, mid-wing land monoplane powered by two 1,700-horsepower Wright Cyclone engines. It became the most heavily armed airplane in the world, was used for high- and low-level bombing, strafing, photoreconnaissance, submarine patrol, and even as a fighter and was distinguished as the aircraft that completed the historic raid over Tokyo in 1942. Normal bomb capacity was 5,000 pounds (2268 kilograms). Some versions carried 75 mm cannon, machine guns and added firepower of 13 .50-caliber guns in the conventional bombardier\'s compartment. One version carried eight .50-caliber guns in the nose in an arrangement that provided 14 forward-firing guns.|http://www.boeing.com/history/products/b-25-mitchell.page</item>
        <item>F-35 Lightning|The F-35A is the U.S. Air Force\’s latest 5th Generation fighter. It will replace the U.S. Air Force\’s aging fleet of F-16 Fighting Falcons and A-10 Thunderbolt II\’s. The F-35 combines 5th Generation fighter aircraft characteristics (including advanced stealth, integrated avionics, sensor fusion and superior logistics support) with the most powerful and comprehensive integrated sensor package of any fighter aircraft in history.|http://www.af.mil/AboutUs/FactSheets/Display/tabid/224/Article/478441/f-35a-lightning-ii-conventional-takeoff-and-landing-variant.aspx</item>
        <item>A-10 Warthog|The A-10 Thunderbolt II has excellent maneuverability at low air speeds and altitude, and is a highly accurate and survivable weapons-delivery platform. The aircraft can loiter near battle areas for extended periods of time and operate in low ceiling and visibility conditions. The wide combat radius and short takeoff and landing capability permit operations in and out of locations near front lines. Using night vision goggles, A-10 pilots can conduct their missions during darkness.|http://www.af.mil/AboutUs/FactSheets/Display/tabid/224/Article/104490/a-10-thunderbolt-ii.aspx</item>
        <item>C-17 Globemaster III|The C-17 Globemaster III is the newest, most flexible cargo aircraft to enter the airlift force. The C-17 is capable of rapid strategic delivery of troops and all types of cargo to main operating bases or directly to forward bases in the deployment area. The aircraft can perform tactical airlift and airdrop missions and can transport litters and ambulatory patients during aeromedical evacuations when required. The inherent flexibility and performance of the C-17 force improve the ability of the total airlift system to fulfill the worldwide air mobility requirements of the United States.|http://www.af.mil/AboutUs/FactSheets/Display/tabid/224/Article/104523/c-17-globemaster-iii.aspx</item>
        <item>A-26 B Lady Liberty|The A-26 is the oldest flying "Invader". Lady Liberty was the 130th produced. The A-26 Invader (B-26 between 1948-1965) was a US twin-engined medium attack bomber built by Douglas during World War II that also saw service during several of the Cold War\’s major conflicts. It served in the USAF in combat thru November 1969. It was designed as a single-pilot aircraft and the first medium bomber to incorporate a laminar flow wing similar to the P-51 Mustang.|http://a26ladyliberty.com/</item>
        <item>AC-47 Gunship Spooky|EMAILED TO ME|http://www.gunshipspooky.com/</item>
        <item>B-17 Texas Raiders|The B-17G Texas Raider began it\'s military career on July 12, 1945. It was officially retired from service on August 25, 1955 where it acquired 3,257 hours of flying time. The aircraft crew consisted of 10: Pilot and So-Pilot, Engineer, Bombardier, Navigator, Radio Operator, Two Waist Gunners, Tail Gunner and Ball Turret Gunner. The B-17 has 12 .50 caliber machine guns and can carry 20,000 lbs maximum bomb load.|http://www.b17texasraiders.org/</item>
        <item>C-1A Miss Belle|Website not working|http://www.traderair.com/\nhttps://www.facebook.com/MissBelleGrummanC1aTraderRestoration/</item>
        <item>CH-47 Chinook|The CH-47D Chinook is the U.S. Army\’s primary heavy troop and supply transport aircraft. Originally fielded in the Vietnam War, the CH-47 has undergone a series up upgrades to increase lift and airworthiness in combat environments. The cockpit can accommodate two pilots and an observer while the cabin has a troop capacity of 33 (36 total). Three M240 7.62 machine guns can be mounted and can also have a suite of countermeasure systems including one or more of the following: a missile approach warner, jammers, radar warner, and chaff/flare dispensers.|http://www.military.com/equipment/ch-47d-chinook</item>
        <item>EC-130H Compass Call|The EC-130H Compass Call is an airborne tactical weapon system using a heavily modified version of the C-130 Hercules airframe. The system disrupts enemy command and control communications and limits adversary coordination essential for enemy force management. The Compass Call system employs offensive counter-information and electronic attack (or EA) capabilities in support of U.S. and Coalition tactical air, surface, and special operations forces. The EC-130H continuously tests new capabilities and tactics to respond to emerging threats and requests from combatant commanders. The EC-130H aircraft carries a combat crew of 13 people. |http://www.af.mil/AboutUs/FactSheets/Display/tabid/224/Article/104550/ec-130h-compass-call.aspx</item>
        <item>KC-135 Stratotanker|"The KC-135 Stratotanker provides the core aerial refueling capability for the United States Air Force and has excelled in this role for more than 50 years. This unique asset enhances the Air Force\'s capability to accomplish its primary mission of global reach. It also provides aerial refueling support to Air Force, Navy, Marine Corps and allied nation aircraft. The KC-135 is also capable of transporting litter and ambulatory patients using patient support pallets during aeromedical evacuations. Four turbofans, mounted under 35-degree swept wings, power the KC-135 to takeoffs at gross weights of up to 322,500 pounds. A cargo deck above the refueling system can hold a mixed load of passengers and cargo. Depending on fuel storage configuration, the KC-135 can carry up to 83,000 pounds of cargo.|http://www.af.mil/AboutUs/FactSheets/Display/tabid/224/Article/104524/kc-135-stratotanker.aspx</item>
        <item>T-1A Jayhawk|The T-1A Jayhawk is a medium-range, twin-engine jet trainer used in the advanced phase of specialized undergraduate pilot training for students selected to fly airlift or tanker aircraft. It is also used to support navigator training for the U.S. Air Force, Navy, Marine Corps and international services. The swept-wing T-1A is a military version of the Beech 400A. It has cockpit seating for an instructor and two students and is powered by twin turbofan engines capable of an operating speed of 538 mph.  |http://www.af.mil/AboutUs/FactSheets/Display/tabid/224/Article/104542/t-1a-jayhawk.aspx</item>
        <item>T-38 Talon|The T-38 Talon is a twin-engine, high-altitude, supersonic jet trainer used in a variety of roles because of its design, economy of operations, ease of maintenance, high performance and exceptional safety record. Air Education and Training Command is the primary user of the T-38 for joint specialized undergraduate pilot training. Air Education and Training Command uses the T-38C to prepare pilots for front-line fighter and bomber aircraft such as the F-15E Strike Eagle, F-15C Eagle, F-16 Fighting Falcon, B-1B Lancer, A-10 Thunderbolt and F-22 Raptor. |http://www.af.mil/AboutUs/FactSheets/Display/tabid/224/Article/104569/t-38-talon.aspx</item>
        <item>T-6A Texan|The T-6A Texan II is a single-engine, two-seat primary trainer designed to train Joint Primary Pilot Training (JPPT), students in basic flying skills common to U.S. Air Force and Navy pilots. Stepped-tandem seating in the single cockpit places one crewmember in front of the other, with the student and instructor positions being interchangeable. A pilot may also fly the aircraft alone from the front seat. Pilots enter the T-6A cockpit through a side-opening, one-piece canopy that has demonstrated resistance to bird strikes at speeds up to 270 knots. The T-6A is used to train JPPT students, providing the basic skills necessary to progress to one of four training tracks: the Air Force bomber-fighter or the Navy strike track, the Air Force airlift-tanker or Navy maritime track, the Air Force or Navy turboprop track and the Air Force-Navy helicopter track. |http://www.af.mil/AboutUs/FactSheets/Display/tabid/224/Article/104548/t-6a-texan-ii.aspx</item>
        <item>UH-60 Blackhawk|The UH-60 Black Hawk helicopter is the U.S. Army\’s primary medium lift utility transport and air assault aircraft. The UH-60 Black Hawk is a twin-engined medium lift utility helicopter. It is equipped with a single 4-bladed rotor and a single 4-bladed tail rotor. The basic crew compliment for the UH-60A is three; pilot, co-pilot, and crew chief. The titanium cored rotor blades are resistant to AAA (anti-aircraft artillery) fire up to 23mm and are equipped with pressurized sensors capable of detecting loss of rotor pressurization (damage). 2 x 7.62 machine guns/150 kt speed/ range 320 nm/max load 2640 lbs or 11 combat-equipped troops) or 4 crew (2 pilots; 2 crew chiefs).|http://www.military.com/equipment/uh-60a-l-black-hawk</item>
        <item>UH-72A Lakota|Airbus Group\’s UH-72A Lakota serves as a key element in the military service\’s modernization of its aviation assets – providing a highly capable helicopter for missions that include homeland security, drug interdiction, general support, logistics and medical evacuation (MEDEVAC). \n\nUH-72A Quick Facts:\nMax. Weight: 7,903 lbs.\nCapacity: 2 pilots + 6 passengers\nPower plant:  2 Turbomeca Arriel 1E2 turboshaft engines \nFast cruise speed: 131 kts.|http://uh-72a.com/index/index.asp</item>
        <item>OPD ABLE 1|Omaha Police Department will have on display the Bell 505 Jet Ranger X. The Bell Helicopter\’s new five-seat aircraft is designed for safety, efficiency and reliability through the use of advanced avionics technology. It incorporates proven dynamic components, advanced aerodynamic design, a dual channel FADEC Turbomeca Arrius 2R engine and best-in-class value.|http://www.bellhelicopter.com/commercial/bell-505</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="exhibitors">
        <item>501st Legion (Star Wars)|The Central Garrison is a unit of the 501st Legion, an all-volunteer, international Star Wars costuming club. The Legion was started in 1997 by a Star Wars fan in South Carolina named Albin Johnson and has since grown to over 6000 members in nearly 50 countries around the world. The Central Garrison has over 100 members and serves Iowa, Minnesota, Nebraska, North Dakota, and South Dakota.|http://www.centralgarrison.com/</item>
        <item>USAF Honor Guard Drill Team|The Drill Team promotes the Air Force mission by showcasing drill performances at public and military venues to recruit, retain, and inspire Airmen. They support Air Force Recruiting Service as the official Ambassadors in Blue.|http://www.honorguard.af.mil/drillteam/</item>
        <item>Vietnam Veterans of America|VVA\’s goals are to promote and support the full range of issues important to Vietnam veterans, to create a new identity for this generation of veterans, and to change public perception of Vietnam veterans|https://vva.org/</item>
        <item>Lincoln Vet Center|?|http://www.va.gov/directory/guide/facility.asp?ID=423</item>
        <item>Civil Air Patrol (CAP)|The Civil Air Patrol Cadet Program offers young adults the opportunity to accomplish real life leadership goals while developing themselves as leaders in the community. Offutt Composite Squadron\'s cadet program allows cadets to manage the cadet program with senior member guidance.  Cadets act as mentors to each other while following a self-study track to advance their own skill and abilities. The cadet program was added to the Civil Air Patrol October 1, 1942 for young adults 15 to 17.|http://offuttcomposite.nebraskacivilairpatrol.org/</item>
        <item>Boy Scouts of America|It is the mission of the Boy Scouts of America, Mid-America council to prepare young people to make ethical and moral choices over their lifetimes by instilling in the them the values of the Scout oath and law.|http://mac-bsa.org/</item>
        <item>Omahawks RC Club|Omahawks RC Inc is the Midwest\'s largest remote control model aircraft facility and is a diverse group of remote control enthusiasts. Originally created in the 1940\'s, the Omahawks have grown from a small grass field to a modern mini-airport with a 500 foot paved runway with enough paved pit area for 75 aircraft.|http://www.omahawks.net/default.asp</item>
        <item>National Weather Service (NWS)|The National Weather Service provides weather, water, and climate data, forecasts and warnings for the protection of life and property and enhancement of the national economy.|http://www.weather.gov/</item>
        <item>Victory Riders|?|?</item>
        <item>Team Red, White &amp; Blue|Team RWB\’s mission is to enrich the lives of America\’s veterans by connecting them to their community through physical and social activities.|http://www.teamrwb.org/</item>
        <item>Sea Cadets|The United States Naval Sea Cadet Corps (USNSCC) was established to create a favorable image of the Navy on the part of the American youth. Their services include to help develop an interest and ability in seamanship and seagoing skills, instill virtues of good citizenship and strong moral principles in each cadet, demonstrate the value of an alcohol-free, drug-free and gang-free lifestyles, and expose cadets to public service and a variety of career paths with our nation\'s armed services.|http://www.seacadets.org/</item>
        <item>561st HHC (Army Reserve)|?|? </item>
        <item>443rd Transportation CO|?|?</item>
        <item>American Legion District 8|The American Legion was chartered and incorporated by Congress in 1919 as a patriotic veterans organization devoted to mutual helpfulness. Focusing on service to veterans, servicemembers and communities, the Legion evolved from a group of war-weary veterans of World War I into one of the most influential nonprofit groups in the United States. Today, membership stands at over 2.4 million in 14,000 posts worldwide. The posts are organized into 55 departments: one each for the 50 states, along with the District of Columbia, Puerto Rico, France, Mexico and the Philippines. National Headquarters for The American Legion is in Indianapolis, Indiana, with an additional office in Washington, DC.|http://www.nebraskalegion.net/index.html</item>
        <item>KIA Honor Flag|KIA Honor Flag Organization has special programs that sponsor KIA Honor Flag packages &amp; services for every Gold Star Family. KIA Honor Flag Representatives, AL, ALR, PGR, VFW, AMVETS, MOPH and similar organizations may also receive KIA Honor Flags or Support Packages at No-Charge to be used for support missions to honor and remember all Americans Killed In Action “KIA” or that have Died Of Wounds “DOW” past or present.|http://www.kiahonorflag.org/</item>
        <item>AAFES|?|https://www.shopmyexchange.com/</item>
        <item>155 CES/CED (EOD)|?|http://www.155arw.ang.af.mil/</item>
        <item>SAC Museum |The Strategic Air Command (SAC) &amp; Aerospace Museum, located between Lincoln and Omaha near Interstate 80, utilizes over 300,000 square feet of exhibit, education, and event space to educate, inspire, and entertain its guests who come from Nebraska, across the country, and around the world.  The museum first opened in 1959 with the mission to commemorate the aircraft of the Strategic Air Command.  The museum became well-known by giving the public the opportunity to visit an impressive array of aircraft that helped SAC preserve the peace during the Cold War.|http://sacmuseum.org/</item>
        <item>Marines|The Marine Corps has been America\'s expeditionary force in readiness since 1775. They are forward deployed to respond swiftly and aggressively in times of crisis. Marines are soldiers of the sea, providing forces and detachments to naval ships and shore operations. They are global leaders, developing expeditionary doctrine and innovations that set the example, and leading other countries\' forces and agencies in multinational military operations. These unique capabilities make them the "First to Fight," and our nation\'s first line of defense.|http://www.marines.com/home</item>
        <item>USAF Academy|The Academy has provided the Air Force with a corps of officers dedicated to upholding the high standards of their profession. The Air Force, in turn has provided a proving ground for these officers and sent back to its Academy dedicated staff members to educate and train these future leaders. Fifty years after the first class entered, the Academy has now graduated over 37,000 young officers\' intent on serving their country.|http://www.usafa.af.mil/</item>
        <item>National Cemetery Administration|NCA honors Veterans and their families with final resting places in national shrines and with lasting tributes that commemorate their service and sacrifice to our Nation.|http://www.cem.va.gov/</item>
        <item>Army|The Army is the largest military branch in the United States. Its job is to protect the country and its citizens. The dominant land power. The Army generally moves in to an area, secures it, and instills order and values before it leaves. It also guards U.S. installations and properties throughout the world.|http://www.goarmy.com/</item>
        <item>Air Force Recruiting|The mission of the United States Air Force is to fly, fight and win in air, space and cyberspace. Our rich history and our vision guide our Airmen as we pursue our mission with excellence and integrity to become leaders, innovators and warriors.|https://www.airforce.com/</item>
        <item>Coast Guard Academy|The U.S. Coast Guard Academy is proud to educate leaders of a multi-mission, maritime military force. Commissioned officers in the Coast Guard lead teams of men and women and are continually called on to serve their community, country and fellow citizens. While the United States Coast Guard is notable as the oldest life-saving service in the world, its roles include more than just maritime safety and security. The Coast Guard is also called upon for critical service in protection of natural resources, maritime mobility (management of maritime traffic, commerce and navigation) and national defense.|http://www.cga.edu/</item>
        <item>West Point|The United States Military Academy\'s mission is to educate, train and inspire the Corps of Cadets so that each graduate is a commissioned leader of character committed to the values of Duty, Honor, Country and prepared for a career of professional excellence and service to the nation as an officer in the United States Army.|http://www.westpoint.edu/SitePages/Home.aspx</item>
        <item>Tuskegee Airmen|"Tuskegee Airmen" refers to the men and women, African-Americans and Caucasians, who were involved in the so-called "Tuskegee Experience", the Army Air Corps program to train African Americans to fly and maintain combat aircraft. The Tuskegee Airmen included pilots, navigators, bombardiers, maintenance and support staff, instructors, and all the personnel who kept the planes in the air.|http://tuskegeeairmen.org/</item>
        <item>VFW|To foster camaraderie among United States veterans of overseas conflicts. To serve our veterans, the military and our communities. To advocate on behalf of all veterans.|http://www.vfw.org/</item>
        <item>USO|For 75 years, the USO has been dedicated to supporting America\’s service members and their loved ones. America\’s 1.3 million active duty service members receive an estimated annual total of 10 million acts of connection from USO centers, services and volunteers.|https://www.uso.org/</item>
        <item>Wounded Warrior Project|Wounded Warrior Project\'s mission is to honor and empower Wounded Warriors. Their vision is to foster the most successful, well-adjusted generation of wounded service members in our nation\'s history. Their purpose is to raise awareness and enlist the public\'s aid for the needs of injured service members, help injured service members aid and assist each other, and provide unique, direct programs and services to meet the needs of injured service members.|https://www.woundedwarriorproject.org/</item>
        <item>Soundz of Freedom|?|http://soundzoffreedom.weebly.com/</item>
        <item>Heartland Organiztion of Rocketry|?|?</item>
        <item>Strike Booster Club|?|?</item>
        <item>VA|?|http://www.va.gov/</item>
        <item>Department of VA Regional Office|?|http://www.benefits.va.gov/lincoln/</item>
        <item>Air Force Reserve Recruiting|?|https://afreserve.com/</item>
        <item>Navy|The mission of the Navy is to maintain, train and equip combat-ready Naval forces capable of winning wars, deterring aggression and maintaining freedom of the seas.|http://www.navy.com/</item>


    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_gmaps">Map</string>
</resources>
